robotis-shop-en.com 2014-05-06

# ROBOTIS - Closer to reaL..

---  
|   
     Home > Privacy Policy |     
---|---  
| 

Sample  
| **1\. Shopping Mall Privacy Policy**  
---  
 ROBOTIS Shop is committed to protecting your personal information ("personal data") while providing the best services possible.

This policy describes the ways in which we collect personal data and the purposes for which it may used. If you object to our use of your personal data in the manner set out in this policy, please inform us by email. 

By using this website you acknowledge that you have read the terms of this policy and that you agree to our use of your personal data as described.  
  
**2\. The data we collect from you**  
**You may be asked to provide us with the following information.**  
  
  * Your Shopping Mall UserName
  * Your name
  * Your address (including zip code) 
  * Your telephone number 
  * Your valid email address

For some of the services supplied on our website, you may be asked to provide further details.  
The information required, and the reason why we need it, will be explained at the time this information is requested.  
  
**3\. Personal Data**  
**a. To provide the Shopping Mall service to you**

We will use your personal data to provide and improve our general service to you, to enable us to deal with any queries you have about our service, and to notify you of any changes to our service and General User Conditions.

 **b. To send you information about our products and services**

From time to time, we will send you information about our products and services which we believe you may be interested in. If you decide now, or at any later time, that you would stop receiving such information, please inform us by e-mail   
  
**4\. Security**  
We operate a number of technical and organizational measures to ensure that your personal data is kept secured and to prevent unlawful or unauthorized disclosure, misuse, alteration, damage or accidental loss or destruction.  
**5\. Notification of changes**  
New services and new laws may generate a need to amend this privacy policy. You should therefore check this privacy policy on a regular basis to ensure you are familiar with its terms.  
**6\. Privacy Support**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us  
  
Privacy Policy    
|   
---  
| | |   
---  
  
#1505 Ace High End Tower No.3, 145 Gasandigital 1-ro, Geumcheongu, Seoul, Korea(153-787) 

﻿Tel : 82-70-8671-2600  Fax :82-70-8230-1336 

COPYRIGHT(C) 2014 [WWW.ROBOTIS.COM](http://www.robotis.com/) ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
